Guide to the Department of Astronomy, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1860-1972; Accession 1977-A-001
  - V. Dirk Brouwer, 1939-1967
    - Departmental correspondence
      - Celestial mechanics: manuscript for Encyclopidia Britanica, undated (Box 61, Folder 53)
      - Choudhry, R.K., 1961, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 54)
      - Civil Defense
        See: box 62, folder 68
      - Clemence, G.M., 1960-1963 (Box 61, Folder 55)
      - Columbia University, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 56)
      - Committee on Space Research (COSPAR) Symposium, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 57)
      - Computer applications to military problems (CAMP), 1959 (Box 61, Folder 58)
      - Computer (Computing) Center, 1957-1962 (Box 61, Folder 59)
      - Computing Center Advisory Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 61, Folder 60)
      - Conference on Radio Astronomy, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 61)
      - Corporation for Economic and Industrial Research (CEIR), 1958 (Box 62, Folder 62)
      - Crone, Ernest, undated (Box 62, Folder 63)
      - D, 1943-1964 (Box 62, Folder 64-66)
      - Davis, Morris, 1946-1947 (Box 62, Folder 67)
      - Defense, 1942-1943 (Box 62, Folder 68)
      - Departmental examinations, undated (Box 62, Folder 69)
      - de Vancouleurs, Gerald H., 1954-1957 (Box 62, Folder 70-71)
      - Disco, A.A., 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 72)
      - Doering, William von E., 1962-1964 (Box 62, Folder 73)
      - Douglas, James N., 1963-1965 (Box 62, Folder 74)
      - Dover Publications, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 75)
      - E, 1943-1963 (Box 63, Folder 76-78)
      - Eckert, Wallace J. (IBM), 1946-1947, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 79)
      - Edwards Street, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 80)
      - Eichhorn, Heinrich, 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 81)
      - Epstein, Isadore, 1963-1965 (Box 63, Folder 82)
      - Exams
        See: box 62, folder 69
      - F, 1943-1965 (Box 63, Folder 83-85)
      - Fellowships and Scholarships, 1950-1960 (Box 63, Folder 86)
      - Ford Foundation Astrograph, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 87)
      - Foundations, undated (Box 63, Folder 88)
      - Fundraising (including Ford Foundation), 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 89)
      - G, 1943-1964 (Box 64, Folder 90-92)
      - Garfinkle, Boris, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 93)
      - G.D. miscellaneous notes, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 94)
      - Gill, Jocelyn R., 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 95)
      - Goddard Space Flight Center, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 96)
      - Grades, 1961-1963 (Box 64, Folder 97)
      - Graduate School, 1943-1962 (Box 64, Folder 98-101)
      - Graduate School applications, 1961-1964 (Box 65, Folder 102-103)
      - Graduate School: Smith Fellowships, 1961-1963 (Box 65, Folder 144)
      - Greenspan, Donald, 1962-1963 (Box 65, Folder 105)
      - H, 1943-1956 (Box 65, Folder 106-110)
      - H, 1957-1965 (Box 66, Folder 111-112)
      - Hamid, Salah, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 113)
      - Herget, Paul, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 114)
      - Hoffleit, Dorrit, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 115)
      - Hori, Gen-ichiro, 1960-1965 (Box 66, Folder 116)
      - I, 1945-1963 (Box 66, Folder 117-118)
      - Institute for Atmospheric Research, 1958-1959 (Box 66, Folder 119)
      - International Astronautical Congress (12 th), 1961 (Box 66, Folder 120)
      - International Astronomical Union
        - 1960-1964 (Box 67, Folder 121-123)
        - Commission 7: Celestial mechanics, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 124)
        - Commission 8: Position Astronomy. Sub-commission 8a: photographic catalogues of stars brighter than the Ninth Magnitude, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 125)
        - Fundraising, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 126)
        - Project West Ford, 1961-1964 (Box 67, Folder 127)
        - U.S.A. National Committee: Sub-Committee for Inter-American Astronomy, 1960-1964 (Box 67, Folder 128)
      - Izsak, Imre G., 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 129)
      - J, 1943-1965 (Box 68, Folder 130-132)
      - Jackson, Cyril (Yale Columbia Southern Station), 1945-1965 (Box 68, Folder 133-139)
      - Johnson, Hollis, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 140)
      - K, 1943-1965 (Box 69, Folder 141-144)
      - Kopal, Zdenck, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 145)
      - Kreiken, E.A., 1963-1964 (Box 69, Folder 146)
      - L, 1943-1964 (Box 69, Folder 147-148)
      - LaPlata Conference, 1960-1961 (Box 69, Folder 149)
      - LeCar, Myron: report on dissertation, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 150)
      - Library, Sterling, 1944-1953 (Box 69, Folder 151)
      - Lilley, A.E., 1959-1962 (Box 69, Folder 152)
      - Liu, Hen-Shou, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 153)
      - LT, undated (Box 70, Folder 154)
      - M, 1943-1965 (Box 70, Folder 155-158)
      - Manuscript material, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 159)
      - Maria Mitchell Association, 1955-1965 (Box 70, Folder 160-162)
      - Math reviews and AMS, 1939-1961 (Box 71, Folder 163)
      - Mc, 1943-1960 (Box 71, Folder 164-165)
      - Measuring Engine (Box 71, Folder 165A)
        See also: box 73, folders 1998-199
      - Meffroy, Jean, 1960-1963 (Box 71, Folder 166)
      - Michelson, Irving, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 167)
      - Mikhailor, A.A., 1960 (Box 71, Folder 168)
      - Miscellaneous notes GDL, undated (Box 71, Folder 169)
      - Morgan, Herbert R., 1947 (Box 71, Folder 170)
      - Moscow, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 171)
      - Move to 135 Prospect Street, 1955-1956 (Box 71, Folder 172)
      - Myint, T.U., 1964 (Box 71, Folder 173)
      - N, 1943-1964 (Box 71, Folder 174-176)
      - National Academy of Sciences
        - National Research Council, 1950-1961 (Box 72, Folder 177)
        - National Research Council, National Science Foundation, Post Doctoral Fellowship Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 178)
        - Watson Fund and Medal, 1960-1961 (Box 72, Folder 179)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration
        - Application for contract (orbit calculation of artificial satellites), 1960 (Box 72, Folder 180)
        - Astronomical Sub-Committee (Selenodesy Working Group), 1963 (Box 72, Folder 181)
        - Contracts NAS 5-728 (53-00-10-0235), 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 182)
        - Contract NAS 5-3131 (53-00-10-0237), 1963 (Box 72, Folder 183)
        - Contract NsG-8-59 (61-54-20-1740), 1959-1961 (Box 72, Folder 184)
        - Contract NsG-8-59 (61-54-20-1740), 1960-1962 (Box 72, Folder 185)
        - Contract NsG 29/60 (61-54-20-1800), 1959-1963 (Box 72, Folder 186)
        - Goddard Space Flight Center, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 187)
        - Jastrow, Robert, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 188)
        - Reports, 1959-1963 (Box 72, Folder 189)
        - Smith, C.V.L., 1961-1964 (Box 72, Folder 190)
        - Traineeships, 1962-1965 (Box 72, Folder 191)
      - National Science Foundation
        - 1951-1963 (Box 73, Folder 192-193)
        - Divisional Committee for Mathematical, Physical and Engineering Sciences, 1957-1958 (Box 73, Folder 194)
        - Grants: miscellaneous, 1956-1958 (Box 73, Folder 195)
        - Grant G3255 (61-54-20-8000) side selection, 1958-1963 (Box 73, Folder 196)
        - Grant G 4172 Relocation of Yale Observatory, 1957-1958 (Box 73, Folder 197)
        - Grant G 5933 Measuring Engine, 1959-1963 (Box 73, Folder 198-199)
        - Grant GP 115 (91-54-37-0115) Symposium on Astrometry, 1962-1964 (Box 73, Folder 200)
      - Navy
        See: box 83, folders 300-301
      - Neighbors (a group of east coast astronomers), 1947 (Box 73, Folder 201)
      - New York Symposium (orbit theory: American Mathematical Society), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 202)
      - News Bureau, 1958-1965 (Box 74, Folder 203)
      - O, 1943-1964 (Box 74, Folder 204-205)
      - Observatory: Astronomical Journal Accounts (standing orders - maintenance), 1960-1967 (Box 74, Folder 206)
        See also: box 60, folder 36 See also: box 73, folder 197
      - Oesterwinter, Claus, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 207)
      - Office of Naval Research (Box 74, Folder 207)
        See also: box 83, folders 300-301
      - Office of Scientific Research (Box 74, Folder 207)
        See also: box 82, folders 285-286
      - Oort, J.H., 1964 (Box 74, Folder 208)
      - P, 1945-1965 (Box 74, Folder 209-211)
      - Page - Liller Report, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 212)
      - Perkin - Elmer Corporation, 1945-1962 (Box 74, Folder 213)
      - Personnel, 1943-1954 (Box 74, Folder 214-215)
      - Personnel, 1955-1961 (Box 75, Folder 216-217)
      - Perth Observatory, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 218)
      - Petty cash, 1943-1959 (Box 75, Folder 219)
      - Pollard, Harry, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 220)
      - President, 1943-1965 (Box 75, Folder 221)
      - Prospect Street (Box 75, Folder 221)
        See also: box 71, folder 172
      - Provost, 1943-1956 (Box 76, Folder 222-224)
      - Provost, 1957-1965 (Box 76, Folder 225-227)
      - Q, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 228)
      - R, 1943-1964 (Box 76, Folder 229-231)
      - Radio Astronomy (Box 76, Folder 232)
        See also: box 62, folder 61
      - Radio Isotopes, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 233)
      - Reports, 1943-1965 (Box 76, Folder 234-235)
      - Rodman, James P., 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 236)
      - Ross, F.E. (Box 76)
        See also: box 74, folder 213
      - S, 1943-1957 (Box 77, Folder 237-242)
      - S, 1958-1965 (Box 78, Folder 243-244)
      - Satellites
        See: box 58, folder 20
      - Schilt, Jan, 1945-1963 (Box 78, Folder 245-248)
      - Schlesinger, Dr. and Mrs. Frank, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 249)
      - Schlesinger Memorial, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 250)
      - Secretary's office, 1943-1955 (Box 79, Folder 251-252)
      - Selective Service, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 253)
      - Service Bureau, 1943-1965 (Box 79, Folder 254-255)
      - Sheffield Scientific School, 1943-1956 (Box 79, Folder 256)
      - Silliman Lectures, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 257)
      - Smith, Harlan, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 258)
      - South African plans, 1948-1950 (Box 79, Folder 259)
      - Southern Hemisphere Astronomy, 1960-1963 (Box 79, Folder 260)
      - Southern Station, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 261)
      - Spitzer, Lyman Jr., 1944-1946 (Box 79, Folder 262)
      - Strömgren, Bengt, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 263)
      - Students, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 264)
      - Summer Conferences, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 265)
      - Summer Employment: enquires, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 266)
      - Summer Institute in Dynamical Astronomy, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 267-268)
      - Symposium on Analynitcal Astrodynamics, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 269)
      - Szebehely, Victor G., 1964 (Box 80, Folder 270)
      - T, 1943-1964 (Box 80, Folder 271)
      - Thesaloniki Symposium (International Astronomical Union) #25, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 272)
      - Travel - D. Brouwer, 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 273)
      - Travel to U.S.S.R., 1960 (Box 80, Folder 274)
      - Treasurer, 1943-1955 (Box 80, Folder 275-276)
      - Treasurer, 1956-1964 (Box 81, Folder 277-278)
      - Pay slips, 1949-1959 (Box 81, Folder 279-280)
      - Remittance slips, 1943-1959
        General note
        See: card file box
      - Sales tax report, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 281)
      - U, 1943-1961 (Box 81, Folder 282)
      - Undergraduate, 1944-1964 (Box 81, Folder 283-284)
      - U.S. Airforce
        - Aeronautical Chart and Information Center, 1961-1963 (Box 82, Folder 285-286)
        - Contracts, 1954-1955 (Box 82, Folder 287)
        - Contract SAR/AF 08(606)-792, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 288)
        - Contract 19 (604)-4137, 1958-1960 (Box 82, Folder 289-290)
        - Contract 19-(604)-4137, 1958-1961 (Box 82, Folder 291)
        - Contract SAR AF (604)3059 Quarterly Report #1 (Lilley), 1958-1959 (Box 82, Folder 292)
        - Contract SAR/AF-AFOSR 397-363 (53-00-20-6397), 1963 (Box 82, Folder 293)
        - Office of Scientific Research Grant AF-AFOSR-397-363, AF-AFOSR-62-380 Research Center for Celestial Mechanics, 1962-1964 (Box 82, Folder 294-295)
        - Office of Scientific Research Mathematical Sciences Advisory Committee, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 296)
      - U.S. Army Corp of Engineers
        - Army Map Service: Contract SAR/DA 419-018 eng - (53-00-50-1880) 2262, 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 297-299)
      - U.S. Navy: Office of Naval Research, 1946-1949 (Box 83, Folder 300-301)
        - Catalogue Verification Project SAR/Nonr 3063(00) (X), 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 302)
        - Catalogue Verification Project SAR/Nonr 609(41) 53-00-71-1641, 1960-1963 (Box 83, Folder 303-304)
          See also: box 83, folders 308-313
        - Contract Nonr 609 (15)Motions of the Principal Planets, 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 305-306)
        - Contract Nonr 1709 (00), 1956 (Box 83, Folder 307)
        - Financial, 1948-1963 (Box 84, Folder 308-313)
        - Financial: audited, 1950-1957 (Box 84, Folder 314)
        - Reports, 1947-1961 (Box 84, Folder 315)
      - V, 1943-1965 (Box 85, Folder 316-318)
      - Vasilerskis, Stanislaus, 1961-1964 (Box 85, Folder 319)
      - Victoria Juan, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 320)
      - W, 1942-1966 (Box 85, Folder 321-325)
      - Watson Astronomical Computing Bureau, 1947 (Box 86, Folder 326)
      - Wesleyan University, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 327)
      - Wesselink, Adrian J., 1964 (Box 86, Folder 328)
      - Westerman, H. Robert, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 329)
      - Wildt, Rupert, 1947, 1960-1964 (Box 86, Folder 330)
      - Winchester Hall, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 331)
      - Wooley, R.v.d.R. (Australia), 1949-1964 (Box 86, Folder 332)
      - X-Y-Z, 1943-1964 (Box 86, Folder 333-334)
      - Yale College
        See: box 81, folders 283-284
      - Yale University: Division of Science, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 335)
    - D. Brouwer and G.M. Clemence, copy of manuscript: Methods of Celestial Mechanics published by Academic Press, pages 1 to 481 and preface notes, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 336-341)
    - Summer Institute in Dynamical Astrology (SIDA)
      - Academic Physics Departments, Directory of, 1961-1962 (Box 88, Folder 342)
      - Activity schedule, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 343)
      - Announcements, application, mailing list, 1959-1961 (Box 88, Folder 344)
      - Announcements, preliminary, 1961-1962 (Box 88, Folder 345-347)
      - Applicants: correspondence, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 348)
      - Applications, 1-40, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 349)
      - Applications
        - A-O, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 350-353)
        - P-Z, 1959 (Box 89, Folder 354-355)
        - A-W, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 356-358)
        - Cancelled, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 359)
        - A-Z, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 360-362)
        - Cancelled, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 363)
        - Late, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 364)
        - List of applicants, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 365)
        - A-Z, 1962 (Box 90, Folder 366-374)
        - Blank, 1962 (Box 90, Folder 375)
        - Cancelled, 1962 (Box 90, Folder 376)
        - Staff, 1962 (Box 90, Folder 377)
        - Cornell University, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 378-379)
        - List of applicants, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 380)
        - A-Z, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 381-383)
        - Requests for, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 384)
      - Banquets, 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 385-386)
      - Books purchased, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 387)
      - Certificated, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 388-389)
      - A Computation of Characteristic Exponents In The Planar Restricted Problem of Three Bodies by André Deprit and J.F. Price, undated (Box 91, Folder 390)
      - Appendix: Computer Program Write-Up Program #36: Non-symmetric orbits with variational solutions, undated (Box 91, Folder 391)
      - Correspondence
        - Albee, Mary, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 392)
        - General, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 393-396)
        - General, 1961, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 397-398)
        - National Science Foundation, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 399)
        - Post institute and other business, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 400)
        - Staff, 1959, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 401-402)
      - Course schedule, 1960-1962 (Box 92, Folder 403-404)
      - Faculty list, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 405)
      - Final reports, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 406-408)
      - Financial
        - Accounts receivable, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 409-410)
        - Advance expenses and requisitions, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 411-412)
        - Expenses, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 413)
        - Forms for bills and requests for checks, 1959-1960 (Box 92, Folder 414-414a)
        - Invoices, 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 415-415a)
        - Invoices, correspondence, memoranda, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 416-417)
        - Report, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 418)
        - Staff stipends and allowances, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 419)
        - Statement, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 420)
      - Handout folder, 1959-1965 (Box 93, Folder 421-424)
      - Housing
        - Accommodations, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 425)
        - Information, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 426)
        - Opportunities, assignments, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 427)
        - Requirements: applicants and staff, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 428)
      - Information, general, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 429)
      - Inquiries, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 430)
      - Lunar theory notes: Dirk Bower, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 431)
      - Meals: A. Daske, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 432)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960-1961, undated (Box 93, Folder 433)
      - Notes, orders for, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 434)
      - Notes: volume IandII, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 435-436)
      - Official business, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 437)
      - Orbit Determination, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 438)
      - Participants: lists, questionnaire results, 1959-1965 (Box 94, Folder 439-442)
      - Participants: stipends and allowances, 1961-1965 (Box 94, Folder 443-444)
      - Participation by category, 1959-1963 (Box 94, Folder 445)
      - Picnics, 1960-1962 (Box 94, Folder 446-447)
      - Post Mortems, 1959-1960 (Box 94, Folder 448)
      - Program in 650 Programming Message, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 449)
      - Program, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 450)
      - Program class, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 451)
      - Proposal: National Science Foundation for Summer Institute, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 452)
      - Proposals for SIDA, 1958-1962 (Box 94, Folder 453)
      - Qualitative Theory of the n-Body Problem: Harry Pollard, undated (Box 94, Folder 454)
      - Questionnaires, 1959-1962 (Box 95, Folder 455-459)
      - Registration: weeks 1-6, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 460)
      - Reports, Final, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 461)
      - Requisition requests, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 462)
      - Solution methods in Canonical Peturbation: John M. Gormally, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 463)
      - Songs, 1960-1965 (Box 95, Folder 464)
      - Special Programs last week of Institute, 1959 (Box 95, Folder 465)
      - Staff, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 466)
      - Staff, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 467)
      - Stencil File, 1961-1962 (Box 96, Folder 468)
      - "Topological approach to the three Body Problem" by Y. Hagihara, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 469)
      - Tuscon, Arizona, University of, 1960-1962 (Box 96, Folder 470-471)
      - Workshop in Orbit Determination: Dr. Kovalevsky, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 472-473)
  - VI. Astronomical Journal, 1941-1969
    - Associate Editors: roster, 1941-1969 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Bank statements, 1958-1965 (Box 97, Folder 2-7)
    - Bills and packing slips, 1958-1964 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Check books, 1958-1967 (Box 97, Folder 9-11)
    - Correspondence
      - A, 1964-1967 (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - American Astronomical Society, 1958-1968 (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - American Astronomical Society: Publication Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 98, Folder 14)
      - American Institute of Physics, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 15)
      - B-G, 1959-1967 (Box 98, Folder 16-21)
      - Goudas paper, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 22)
      - H-I, 1959-1965 (Box 98, Folder 23-24)
      - J, 1960-1965 (Box 99, Folder 25)
      - Johnson Reprint Corporation, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 26)
      - K-L, 1963-1965 (Box 99, Folder 27-28)
      - Lancaster Press, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 29)
      - Lyttleton-Stromberg, 1958-1959 (Box 99, Folder 30)
      - M, 1958-1965 (Box 99, Folder 31-32)
      - MaiCing Permit, 1958-1962 (Box 99, Folder 33)
      - N, 1960-1965 (Box 99, Folder 34)
      - National Science Foundation, 1953-1966 (Box 99, Folder 35)
      - O, 1960-1965 (Box 99, Folder 36)
      - Observatory Reports, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 37)
      - P, 1960-1964 (Box 99, Folder 38)
      - R-Z, 1963-1966 (Box 100, Folder 39-46)
    - Financial statements, 1934-1968 (Box 100, Folder 47-48)
    - Production Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 100, Folder 49)
    - Volume and issue information (V.47-70), 1938-1965 (Box 100, Folder 50)
    - Receipt book, 1959-1962 (Box 101, Folder 51)
  - VII. Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy, Inc, (AURA), 1965-1972
    - Associated Universities, Incorporated, 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors: minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 102, Folder 2-5)
    - By-Laws, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Carnegie Institution of Washington: Southern Observatory (CARSO), 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Cerro Tololo Inter-Ameridan Observatory: Policy manual, 1970 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Chile Site Survey Reports, Nos. 26-31, undated (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee: minutes, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Kitt Peak National Observatory (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Planetary Sciences Division: Report to Planetary Sciences Subcommittee, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Policy Manual and revisions, 1968-1971 (Box 103, Folder 12-13)
      - Solar Division: Report to the Solar Subcommittee, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - National Science Foundation, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Planetary Sciences Subcommittee: minutes, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Scientific Committee: Correspondence and minutes, 1962-1972 (Box 103a, Folder 17-22)
    - Scientific Committee: correspondence and minutes, 1962-1972 (Box 103b, Folder 23-26)
    - Stellar Astronomy: subcommittee minutes, 1970 (Box 103b, Folder 27)
    - Telescope loan: University of Michigan, 1971-1972 (Box 103b, Folder 28)
    - Telescope move: Yale to Cerro Tololo Inter-American Observatory, 1972 (Box 103b, Folder 29)
    - Visiting Committee, 1971 (Box 103b, Folder 30)
  - VIII. Research Data, 1874-1962
    - Yale Telescope volumes
      - 1-7, 1925-1926 (Box 104)
      - 8-14, 1926-1927 (Box 105)
      - 15-21, 1927-1928 (Box 106)
      - 22-28, 1928 (Box 107)
      - 29-35, 1928-1929 (Box 108)
      - 36-42, 1929-1930 (Box 109)
      - 43-49, 1930-1931 (Box 110)
      - 50-56, 1931 (Box 111)
      - 57-63, 1931-1932 (Box 112)
      - 64-70, 1932-1933 (Box 113)
      - 71-77, 1933-1934 (Box 114)
      - 78-84, 1934-1935 (Box 115)
      - 85-91, 1935-1937 (Box 116)
      - 92-98, 1937-1938 (Box 117)
      - 99-105 (106, 107 lacking), 1938-1939 (Box 118)
      - 108-112, 1939-1940 (Box 119)
      - 113-119, 1940-1942 (Box 120)
      - 120-126, 1942-1944 (Box 121)
      - 127-133, 1944-1946 (Box 122)
      - 134-140, 1946-1947 (Box 123)
      - 141-147, 1947-1948 (Box 124)
      - 148-154, 1948-1950 (Box 125)
      - 155-161, 1950-1957 (Box 126)
      - 162-168, 1957-1961 (Box 127)
      - 169-172, miscellaneous (1928-1936), 1961-1962 (Box 128)
    - Tables, miscellaneous and research notes
      - Occultations: Tashkent, Frederica, Copenhagen, Hellerup, Besancon, Bridgeport, Bethlehem (PA), Los Angeles, Aarhuus, Amherst, Florence, Leonia, Cambridge (MA), Kiev, Tomsk, Zo-Se, Fannerup, Nyborg, South Hadley, Tokyo, 1928 (Box 129, Folder 173)
      - Washington: 23 occultations, 1928 (Box 129, Folder 174)
      - Occultations by the moon, 1928 January (Box 129, Folder 175)
      - Strasbourg, 20 occultations; Omaha 8 occultations; Parsgrund, 2 occultations, 1928 (Box 129, Folder 176)
      - Occultations, 1926 (Box 129, Folder 177)
      - Observations, 1927 (Box 129, Folder 178)
      - Leo (Leonia) 14 occultations Georgetown Coll. Obs. 32 occulations, 1927 (Box 129, Folder 179)
      - L.P. (La Plata) 12 occultations, 1927 (Box 129, Folder 180)
      - Occultations: Kiew, Florence, Warsaw, Turin, 1927 (Box 129, Folder 181)